Find Your Flock
Storks is a adventure, animation, comedy film directed by Doug Sweetland.
Storks deliver babies…or at least they used to.
Now they deliver packages for a global internet retail giant.
Junior, the company’s top delivery stork, is about to be promoted when he accidentally activates
the Baby Making Machine, producing an adorable and wholly unauthorized baby girl...
Junior (voice), played by Andy Samberg.
Tulip (voice), played by Katie Crown.
Hunter (voice), played by Kelsey Grammer.
Sarah Gardner (voice), played by Jennifer Aniston.
Henry Gardner (voice), played by Ty Burrell.
Nate Gardner (voice), played by Anton Starkman.
Storks is a 2016 American animated adventure comedy film directed by
Nicholas Stoller and Doug Sweetland, and written by Stoller.
The film features the voices of Andy Samberg, Kelsey Grammer, Katie Crown,
Keegan-Michael Key, Jordan Peele, Jennifer Aniston, Ty Burrell, and Danny Trejo.
The film follows two distribution centre employees—hotshot package delivering stork Junior and his
human colleague Tulip—who accidentally create a baby using a defunct baby factory.
In order to protect the baby from the company's manager, the two
embark on a journey to deliver the baby to her family.
The project was announced by Warner Animation Group in January 2013, with
Sweetland attached to direct, and Stoller hired to write the screenplay.
It was announced in April 2015 that Stoller and Sweetland would co-direct the
film, and Stoller would produce the film alongside Brad Lewis.
The main cast was announced soon after.
Mychael and Jeff Danna composed the film's musical score.
The animation was provided by Sony Pictures Imageworks.
Storks premiered at the Regency Village Theater in Los Angeles, California on September 17,
2016, and was theatrically released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on September 23.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the
animation, humor and voice acting, but criticized the story.
It was a commercial success, earning $183 million against a $70 million budget.
The film explores themes of baby, villain, stork, delivery service.
The tone is lighthearted.